rhizome.org 2003-06-29

# Rhizome.org: Info--Privacy Statement

Rhizome.org is committed to protecting your privacy. If you have provided us with your name, email address or other personal information, we will hold that information in the strictest confidence. We will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [info@rhizome.org](mailto:info@rhizome.org).

**Member Registration**

In order to access certain services offered at Rhizome.org, you need to register as a member by providing some personal information, including your email address. When you register you may also choose to provide additional personal information, including biographical information, as part of your member profile. You decide whether to make your name and any other personal information available to other Rhizome.org members in our community directory. We will not disclose your personal information in the community directory unless you have authorized us to do so, and we will not disclose your personal information to others unless required to do so by law.

We may use the information that you provide to invite you to events in your local area, to update you on new developments at Rhizome.org or to send you fundraising appeals. If you don't want to receive such emails, you can opt out on the Rhizome.org web site. You may also choose to complete a voluntary demographic questionnaire. We use aggregated demographic information about our members (such as the total number of members, the countries they represent, their average income, etc.) in our marketing, publicity and fundraising materials.

You can update your information and preferences at any time on the Rhizome.org web site.

**Cookies**

After you've registered, we use "cookies" to recognize your browser so you don't have to sign in every time you return to our site. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used for convenience and are in no way linked to any personally identifiable information such as your name or email address. Many web browsers allow you to block cookies.

**Online Transactions Via the Secure Server**

Rhizome.org takes every precaution to protect data such as credit card numbers transferred via our secure server. We use high level SSL and PGP encryption software to receive online credit card information.

**Email Lists**

We use email list software to manage our email publications, including Rhizome Raw, Rhizome Rare, Rhizome Digest and Net Art News. The addresses on our subscriber lists are password protected and can only be accessed by Rhizome staff.

**Statistical Information**

Statistical information such as Web site traffic is collected and logged by our Web server. In some cases, this information is used in creative ways. For example, the Rhizome interface StarryNight records hits for individual items in the Rhizome archive then displays this information visually. This statistical data has no connection to personally identifiable information such as your name or email address.

**Notification of Changes**

This privacy policy is posted on the Rhizome.org web site. If at any time we substantively modify this policy, we will update this document and notify our members via email.
